<resources>
    <string name="app_name">City Tour Guide</string>

    <string-array name="cityNames">
        <item>New Delhi</item>
        <item>Mumbai</item>
        <item>Hyderabad</item>
        <item>Bangalore</item>
        <item>Ahmedabad</item>
        <item>Chennai</item>
        <item>Kolkata</item>
        <item>Jaipur</item>
        <item>Lucknow</item>
        <item>Bhopal</item>
        <item>Patna</item>
        <item>Ranchi</item>
        <item>Chandigarh</item>
        <item>Guwahati</item>
        <item>Dhanbad</item>
        <item>Bhubaneswar</item>
        <item>Deharadun</item>
        <item>Imphal</item>
        <item>Gaya</item>
        <item>Pondicherry</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="shortDescription">
    <item>Things to see and do in Delhi and New Delhi are plentiful and include experiencing its diverse arts and crafts industry. Its many magnificent monuments, countless performing arts venues, and its excellent cuisine, including delicacies from every corner of India. Delhi is also a shopper\'s paradise with numerous bazaars and markets, including Chandni Chowk, the country\'s most famous commercial area.</item>
    <item>Mumbai formerly called Bombay is a melting pot of cultures that offer memorable experiences. The commercial capital of India is home of entrepreneurs, dreamers, sky-touching concrete towers, thriving nightlife, cricket, Bollywood and so much more. Undoubtedly, Mumbai is one of the must- visit places in India. Mumbai tours lure history lovers, culture enthusiasts, experience-seekers and tourists from all walks of life.</item>
    <item>Hyderabad city is the capital city of the Indian state of Telangana. The bustling city is home to a number of bazaars, thanks to its history as a trading hub. It is also home to heritage buildings like the Golconda Fort, Qutb Shahi tombs, Chowmahalla Palace and, of course, the iconic Charminar at the centre of Old Hyderabad.</item>
    <item>Fondly known as ‘Garden City’, Bengaluru is the land of myriad charms. Ranking among the leading metropolises in India, the city deserved to be a part of tours in India. Tree-lined streets and the abundant greenery is the reason behind its named.</item>
    <item>Ahmedabad, also known as Amdavad, is one of the largest cities of India and the former capital of Gujarat. This city of famous tourist attractions is situated on the banks of Sabarmati river and is known for its world-famous cotton textiles, a wide variety of mouth-watering snacks, diamond cutting, and much more. </item>
    <item>Chennai is major city of southern India, is a busy port on the southeastern coast. A center of music, dance, and the fine arts, Madras gives the visitor a colorful picture of Hindu life. Hindu temples built between A.D. 600 and 1600 are found throughout the area. </item>
    <item>The city is famously known as the Land of Mother Teresa and Rabindra Nath Tagore, but in the heart of the 300-year old city is the real feel of India. Kolkata tours offers an insight into the historic and cultural legacy of India. Beyond its tourist attractions, it serves as the gateway to the East and the North East India. </item>
    <item>Jaipur also known as the ‘Pink City’ is the capital of the North Indian State of Rajasthan. Named after its founder Maharaja Jai Singh II (1693-1743), this royal city of the former Rajputana is one of the most glorious places to visit in India. Jaipur tours are perfect for history lovers, the cultural enthusiasts and visitors who love to be pampered by royal hospitality. </item>
    <item>Lucknow is the capital city of the north Indian state of Uttar Pradesh. This metro city is the administrative headquarters of Lucknow District and Lucknow Division. Lucknow has always been known as a multicultural city and flourished as a cultural and artistic capital of North India in the 18th and 19th centuries. </item>
    <item>Bhopal is the capital city of the state of Madhya Pradesh, which is the largest state in India. Bhopal is also referred to as the City of Lakes because of the two beautiful lakes that are situated in the center of the city. Apart from its natural beauty, Bhopal is also famous for its mosques. </item>
    <item>Patna is the capital city of the Indian state of Bihar. It is a very old city and has a history of at least 2,500 years. It was famous for its educational institutes, which during those days, attracted scholars from all over the world. Gautama Buddha who started Buddhism had also visited this city.</item>
    <item>Popularly referred to as the City of Waterfalls, Ranchi is a beautiful destination full of natural and cultural wonders, with opportunities for trekking through bamboo covered topography and feasting on regional delicacies like \'Golgappas\', discovering Rabindranath Tagore\'s literary sanctuary at Tagore Hill.</item>
    <item>Chandigarh city is the capital of the territory and of the states of Haryana and Punjab. Chandigarh\'s name, meaning “stronghold of the goddess Chandi,” is derived from the Chandi Mandir, a temple dedicated to the goddess that is located near the town of Mani Majra. Area union territory, 44 square miles (114 square km).</item>
    <item>Dotted with ancient temples, Guwahati is also known as the \'City of Temples\'. It is one of the fastest developing cities of India. According to a survey done by a UK media outlet, Guwahati is among the 100 fastest growing cities of the world, and is the 5th fastest growing city in India. </item>
    <item>The city is called the \'Coal Capital of India\' for housing one of the largest coal mines of India. The prestigious institute, Indian School of Mines (now IIT Dhanbad) is situated in Dhanbad. Dhanbad has a large mix of different cultures and people. There is a significant percentage of people who are Bengalis, Biharis and locals. There are also significant Gujarati, Punjabi and Tamil, Malayali, Telugu, Marwari Rajasthani communities who have been living in dhanbad for a long time. Therefore, Dhanbad can be called a cultural melting pot. This diversity is also mirrored in the fact that there are a large number of languages spoken in Dhanbad.</item>
    <item>Bhubaneswar (Bhubaneswar means the Land of God, Bhuban - earth or land and Eswar - God) is the capital city of the Indian Middle Eastern state of Orissa (Odisha). Bhubaneswar has an ancient history that goes back more than 2300 years when it was treat as the capital (Sisupalgarh) city of Kalinga Kingdom. During a destructive war of Kalinga near Dhauli between Maurya Empire (the Great Ashoka) and Kalinga Empire (Queen Padmavati, supposed) in 260 BC was taken.</item>
    <item>The capital of Uttarakhand, Dehradun is a gateway to some of the most popular hill stations in the country like Nainital and Mussoorie. Nestled in the Doon Valley, it is primarily known for the number of elite boarding schools it has like the Doon School and the Indian Military Academy. Dehradun is located in the Doon Valley on the foothills of the Himalayas nestled between Song river, a tributary of Ganga on the east and the Asan river, a tributary of Yamuna on the west. The city is noted for its picturesque landscape and slightly milder climate and provides a gateway to the surrounding region.</item>
    <item>Imphal is the capital city of the Indian state of Manipur. The metropolitan centre of the city contains the ruins of Kangla Palace (also known as Kangla Fort), the royal seat of the former Kingdom of Manipur, surrounded by a moat. Situated 786 m above sea level, Imphal is known for its scenic landscapes and greenery. Manipur is a land of many tribes and Imphal is the cultural capital of the state.</item>
    <item>Gaya is mostly known as the birthplace of Buddhism as Gautama Buddha attained nirvana in this holy site. Gaya has temples of great beauty and heritage and makes it one of the most desired spiritual destinations in India. The beautiful city is surrounded on three sides by hills and the meandering Phalgu River.</item>
    <item>Pondicherry is the capital and the most-populous city of the Union Territory of Puducherry in India. The city is in the Puducherry district on the southeast coast of India and is surrounded by the state of Tamil Nadu, with which it shares most of its culture, heritage and language.</item>
</string-array>

    <string-array name="delhi">
        <item><i><font color="red">India Gate</font></i>\nLooking a little like the famous Arc de Triomphe in Paris, the equally impressive India Gate is a magnificent stone arch built as a memorial to Indian soldiers killed in WWI. An eternal flame burns beneath the massive structure, and its walls are inscribed with the names of more than 90,000 soldiers who died in the conflict.
                Standing on a base of red stone and featuring a shallow domed bowl on top that is occasionally filled with burning oil (usually only on important anniversaries), the structure dominates the parkland around it, an always busy area with crowds of tourists and locals alike enjoying a picnic or simply relaxing. For a real treat, try to see the India Gate at night, considered one of the top free things to do in New Delhi. it\'s a spectacular sight when it and nearby fountains are floodlit.</item>
        <item><b>The Red Fort</b>\nThe beautiful Red Fort was built by Shah Jahan in 1648 and served as the seat of Mughal power until 1857. This stunning structure, with its tall, red sandstone walls covers an area of more than two square kilometers, the entirety of which is crescent shaped and surrounded by a moat. The impressive main entrance, the Lahore Gate, is so named as it faces towards Lahore in Pakistan, while the even grander Delhi Gate was used by the emperor for ceremonial processions.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="mumbai">
        <item>Gateway of India\nGateway of India, the best place to visit in Mumbai, was built in 1924 by George Willet to honor the visit of King George V and Queen Mary to Mumbai. Visit this place in the early morning or late evening hours to enjoy the cool breeze of the sea with your family sans the crowd. Located next to the iconic Taj Mahal Palace and facing the vast Arabian Sea, the Gateway of India leaves you spellbound in every way possible. Take a ferry ride offered here to experience a stupendous view of this monument right from the sea and you can also visit other main attractions nearby.</item>
        <item>Elephanta Caves Take a tour to this UNESCO World Heritage Site in Mumbai and get wonderstruck by the massive rock-cut caves that date back to several centuries. It has five caves dedicated to Hindu god Shiva and two caves depicting Buddhist architectures. To reach this place, you need to take a one-hour ferry ride from the Gateway of India, during which you can also enjoy the scenic beauty of Mumbai. Those who lack the spirit of a trekker can hop on the toy train that will take you on a tour of the caves right from the entry point. The restaurant and canteen run by MTDC can take care of your hunger pangs. If you are planning a one-day tour to the Elephanta Caves, this blog will give you more details.</item>
        <item>Siddhivinayak Temple\nOne of the most frequented temples in Mumbai, the Siddhivinayak Temple is dedicated to Lord Ganesh. Devotees from across India including famous personalities from Bollywood and sports throng the temple to seek the blessings of Siddhivinayak Ganapati. The auspicious idol of Lord Ganesha is carved out in a single black stone with the trunk bent towards right making it one-of-its-kind. You can plan a visit to this temple with your family for an enriched spiritual experience.</item>
        <item>ISKCON Temple\nAlso known as Sri Sri Radha Rasabihari ji Temple, it is close to Juhu Beach and boasts 4 acres of land area. The gorgeously carved temple draws Hindu devotees in droves and hosts festivals like Ratha Yatra, Janmashtami, Radhasthami, Makarsankranti, and Gaura Purnima with great pomp and show. Crafted with marble, the temple comes with a 7-storey guesthouse, an auditorium, and a restaurant to help devotees attend spiritual programs with ease. The ISKCON Temple is also an educational hub and its library houses an impressive collection of spiritual books. </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hyderabad">
        <item>Char Minar\nThe epic signature of the city, Char Minar makes for a wonderful sight. Located in the heart of Hyderabad’s old city, surrounded by Mecca Masjid, built using bricks from Mecca and Laad Bazaar - a boisterous shopping street, this landmark is laced in history.\nBuilt in 1591 by Muhammad Quli Qutub Shah, it was constructed to commemorate the founding of Hyderabad and also to ward of a deadly epidemic that was rampant then in the Golconda region. Graced by 4 minarets soaring almost 50ft in height, it has a mosque and 45 prayer spaces is amongst the famous places in Hyderabad.</item>
        <item>Golconda Fort\n"A medieval fort now overlooking the city, Golconda is one of the historical places to visit in Hyderabad. Originally built in mud on a 400ft hill, the fort ruins of today have seen the reign of several dynasties. Situated 11km away from the bustling urbanism of Hyderabad, it derives its name from a Telugu word meaning Shepherd’s Hill. Reminiscence of a well-planned Golconda city within the fortress limits is evident even now.\nThe remains of multiple fortification layers, armories, magazines, mosques, granaries, reservoirs, audience chambers and royal dwellings complement the striking appearance of the fort.\n" +Famous for its acoustics, a unique signalling device that was incorporated in its construction, the structure is known for its palaces, ingenious water supply system and the famous Fateh Rahben, one of the cannons used in the last siege of Golconda by Aurangzeb. The Sound and Light show brings alive the grandeur of one of India’s famous forts.\n</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="bangalore">
        <item>Bangalore palace\nThe majestic Bangalore palace is a royal palace known for its architecture with beautiful carvings both inside and outside. It is owned by the Mysore Royal family. The sprawling grounds around the palace is ideal for a picnic.\n</item>
        <item>National Gallery of Modern Art\nNational Gallery of Modern Art is a two-storeyed museum based in a colonial-style residential building. It showcases the cultural ethos of India from periods as early as the 18th century. There is also a huge auditorium, a charming cafeteria, and a reference library here.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ahemdabad">
        <item>Dada Hari Wav\nBuilt by a woman of Sultan Begara\'s harem in 1499AD, these step-wells were made as a retreat during hot summers. Waiting to be filled with rain water, no matter what the weather is, it is always cooler within the Step-wells.\n</item>
        <item>Statue of Unity\nStatue of Unity is a memorial to The Iron Man of India, Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel. The Bronze statue stands 182 metres tall and is the \'Tallest statue in the World\'. The statue of Unity is located in Gujrat, by the banks of River Narmada on the River Island of Sadhu Bet overlooking the Narmada Dam (Sardar Sarovar Dam) from 3.2 km away.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="chennai">
        <item>Government Museum\nGovernment Museum was established in 1851 and is the second oldest museum in the country after the Indian Museum in Kolkata. Situated in Egmore suburb of Chennai, it is built in the Indo-Sarcenic style and houses a rich collection of the works of Raja Ravi Varma.</item>
        <item>Marundeeswarar Temple\nThe magnificent Marundeeswarar Temple, in Tiruvanmiyur, near Chennai has the temple deity Shiva in the form of Marundeeswar or Aushadeeswarar, the God of Medicines. A fine specimen of Dravidian architecture, this temple is a must visit for anyone visiting Chennai or nearby cities.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="kolkata">
        <item>Victoria Memorial\nThe Victoria Memorial is a large marble building, which is considered to be the pride of Kolkata. Built between 1906 and 1921, it is dedicated to the memory of Queen Victoria. Now, it is a museum and a popular tourist spot under the Ministry of Culture.\n</item>
        <item>Fort William\nFort William is a fort built in Kolkata on the eastern banks of the River Hooghly, the major distributary of Ganges. The magnificent structure is spread over 70.9 acres and is embellished with hundreds of arched windows that overlook lush green gardens. Meticulous stonework adorns the surface of the building.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="jaipur">
        <item>Amber Fort\nCradled on the top of a hill near Jaipur lies the Amer Fort, one of the most magnificent palaces in India. Also commonly known as the Amber Fort, this majestic building with its maze-like passages and serpentine staircases is an architectural masterpiece and with significant importance in Indian history.\n</item>
        <item>City Palace\nThe City Palace is the main palace from where the Maharaja reigned from. The palace includes the Chandra Mahan and Mubarak Mahal along with various other buildings within the complex. It is located towards the north-eastern side of Jaipur. The palace is divided into a series of courtyards, buildings and gardens including the Chandra Mahal and the Mubarak Mahal. The museum showcases various unique handcrafted products and other things that belong to the royal heritage of the City Palace.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="lucknow">
        <item>Bara Imambara\nThe Bara Imambara of Lucknow is one of the most famous monuments of the city. Also known as Asfi Imambara, after the name of the Nawab of Lucknow who got it constructed, it is an important place of worship for the Muslims who come here every year to celebrate the religious festival of Muharram. The Imambara is specially known for its incredible maze, known as Bhul Bhulaiya locally, which is located in the upper floor of the monument.\n</item>
        <item>British Residency\nThe British Residency of Lucknow served as a refuge for several Britishers during the uprising on 1857. The fort is now in ruins and a cemetery nearby contains the graves of the hundreds of Britishers who died during the siege. The ruins are now protected by the Archaeological Survey of India.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="bhopal">
        <item>Indira Gandhi Rashtriya Manav Sangrahalaya\nThe IGRMS, or Museum of Humankind, is a museum that tries to depict the evolution of man and humankind with special reference to India. The museum is spread over an area of a sprawling 200 acres. Exhibitions telling the story of Human life and culture are presented in the Museum all year long.\n</item>
        <item>Bhimbetka Rock Shelters\nBhimbetka is a world heritage site and houses one of the oldest cave paintings in the world. A must-visit for all history-enthusiasts, Bhimbetka gives a sneak-peek into the pre-historic era.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="patna">
        <item>Patna Sahib Gurudwara\nThis Gurudwara was built by Maharaja Ranjit Singh in remembrance of Guru Gobind Singh Ji, Patna being his birthplace. He was the 10th and the last Guru of Sikhs.\n</item>
        <item>Golghar\nA building in the shape of a beehive, Golghar originally served the purpose of a storehouse. It was built in 1786 by Captain John Garstin and provides a panoramic view of the entire city along with the River Ganga.\n</item>
        <item>Bihar Museum\nBihar Museum is one of the famous attractions in Patna built to provide insights into the history of Bihar and inculcate a sense of respect and pride in the hearts of the current generation. The museum is a recent addition to the list of attractions in the city. One of the main reasons for establishing the museum was to create more space to house and exhibit artefacts since the century-old Patna Museum is running out of space. Since there was little scope to relocate installed artefacts, the decision of keeping the focus on Human History was taken. Therefore, the Bihar Museum is where visitors can find information about the human history of Bihar to a large extent. The displays include ancient artefacts of artistic heritage, artworks belonging to various tribes and insights into the past and present of Bihar.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ranchi">
        <item>Patratu Valley\nForty kilometres outside Ranchi lies the scintillating Patratu Valley. With sparkling waters of the Patratu Dam on one side and lush green trees flanked along the other, driving along the Ghat of the Patratu Valley is truly a stupendous experience. However, do not venture into these roads after dark because of the rampant Naxalite influence in the area.\n</item>
        <item>Jagannath Temple\nPerched up on a hilltop, the Jagannath Temple is the most popular historical landmark in Ranchi dating back to 1691. As s smaller replica of the Jagannath Temple in Puri, the temple is decked with intricate carvings and a unique blend of coloured stones. The Rath Yatra is a festival of joyous celebration that sees a footfall of thousands of tourists each year.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="chandhigarh">
        <item>Rock Garden\nThe Rock Garden is a massive open-air exhibition hall that displays sculptures made from urban and industrial wastes that have been designed and executed by Nek Chand. It also consists of man-made interlinked waterfalls. The popular Teej festival is also celebrated here each year.\n</item>
        <item>Thunder Zone\nAnother fantasy park in the hub of the city, Thunderzone offers extensive range of exciting rides like Swinging Chairs, Octopus, Cater Pillar, Mono Junction, Columbus, Sun N Moon, Striking Cars, Baby Train, Splash, COBF Music Bob, and Wet Park.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="guwhati">
        <item>Umananda Temple\nUmananda Temple is a Shiva temple located on the Peacock Island, in the middle of river Brahmaputra. Peacock Island, which houses the Umanada Temple, is known as smallest inhabited riverine island in the world. Country boats are available all the time during the day, on the banks of Brahmaputra, to take the visitors to the island. The mountain on which the temple has been built, is known as Bhasmacala.\n</item>
        <item>Kamakhya Temple\nThe Kamakhya temple is one of the most revered shrines of Shakti in India, in the form of Kamakhya. Located on the Nilachal Hills just 7km from Guwahati, the Kamakhaya temple is of great religious importance. It also holds tremendous historic and archeological significance.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="dhanbad">
        <item>Topchanchi Lake\nLocated on the NH2, Golden Quadrilateral, Topchanchi Lake is an artificial lake covering an expanse of over 214 acres. The lake is at a distance of 37 kilometres from the Dhanbad Railway Station and is a famous spot for tourists to indulge in nature walks, exploration as well as hold picnics. The Topchanchi Lake expanse consists of the marvellous artificial lake amidst the rolling green hills and forests as well as the famous Prasanath Hills nearby. Part of the 214 acres or more precisely 8.7 square kilometres, is also dedicated to a wildlife sanctuary. Due to this reason, you will find small, harmless animals roaming around the Lake as well. Nature lovers enjoy this part of town and are often found flocking the area in search of rare flora and fauna.\n</item>
        <item>Birsa Munda Park\nBirsa Munda Park has the distinction of being the only park in the city of Dhanbad. It is a major tourist attraction spread over 21 acres of land having a walking path, lawns, a canteen, a playground and toy rides for children. The Birsa Munda Park was opened in November 2009 and has since contributed immensely to the growth of the region. It is often regarded as the stepping stone to various other projects that are coming up in the city. Birsa Munda Park is rightly counted as a must-visit destination and offers varied activities for people of all age groups.\n</item>
        <item>Shakti Mandir\nThe Shakti Mandir is one of the pride of Dhanbad and gathers several devotees to the city all year round. The temple is located in the very heart of the city on the Thorapathak Road and is devoted to the Goddess Durga. The reason for the temple standing out amongst the several temples situated here, being a nationally known temple is the fact that Shakti Mandir owns the Akhand Jyoti or the eternal flame which is brought down from Vaishno Devi. The sacred temple is thus crowded on special occasions such as Diwali, Dussehra, and Tuesdays and Fridays of every week, which is considered as unique by devotees of the Goddess.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="bhubaneswar">
        <item>Lingaraj Temple\nThe Lingaraj Temple is an ancient temple with great religious importance. Dedicated to Lord Shiva as the name suggests, it is visited by huge number of devotees throughout the year.\n</item>
        <item>Parasurameswara Temple\nConstructed in 650 A.D. this temple is a unique specimen of Oriyan style of architecture. The most special feature of this temple is the presence of one thousand lingas in the north-west corner of the complex.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="dehradun">
        <item>Robber\'s Cave\nNestled within a suburb of Dehradun, Robber\'s Cave is popularly called Guchhipani or Guchu Pani. It is a magnificient gorge between a limestone formation. Surrounded by majestic hills and offers a glorious trek up the mountains, it makes for one of the best attractions near Dehradun.\n</item>
        <item>Sahastradhara\nSahastradhara meaning \'thousand fold spring\' is popular for its ecstatic beauty and therapeutic value since its water contains Sulphur. While the place can be visited any time during the year, you would love the charming beauty of the waterfall during rainy season when the stream proposes the appearance of a gushing torrent.\n</item>
        <item>Tapkeshwar Temple\nTapkeshwar is a famous cave temple on the banks of a rivulet. The water further flows in to the cave to drip on to the Shiv Linga inside. Sulphur springs present around the temple makes for a therapeutic bath.\n</item>
        <item>Mindrolling Monastery\nMindrolling, which means "Place of Perfect Emancipation" in Tibetan language, is the largest Buddhist Vihara of India, training monks for over 300 years.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="imphal">
        <item>Kangla Fort\nAlso known as the Palace of Kangla, this place situated on the banks of the Imphal river, served as the royal palace of King Pakhangba. After 2003 this fort has been open for public viewing. It has historical as well as archaeological significance which makes it a great tourist attraction.\n</item>
        <item>Tharon Cave\nA 655.6 m long cave, this cave can be explored inside out by enthusiasts, with the help of the map drawn outside the cave. It attracts tourists interested in an adventurous experience. It is also spelled as the Thaeuluan Cave.\n</item>
        <item>Shaheed Minar\nThis 11 m tall tower is situated in the centre of the Bir Tirkendrajit Park and is a memorial for those who died against the British while fighting in the Meitei Revolt in 1891.\n</item>
        <item>INA Memorial\nOnce used as the unofficial headquarters of the Indian National Army, this memorial was built to honour the soldiers who had sacrificed their lives for India. Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose motivated and formed armies here to participate in the freedom struggle.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="gaya">
        <item>Mahabodhi Temple\nThe Mahabodhi Temple serves to be the main and most important attraction in Bodh Gaya. It was built in the 7th century, surrounding the Bodhi Tree that Buddha sat under whilst he attained enlightenment.\n</item>
        <item>Great Buddha Statue\nThis statue of Lord Buddha is the tallest in India and was instated by the XIV Dalai Lama in 1989. It is a meditating Buddha resting on a giant lotus, constructed using intricately carved sandstone and red granite.\n</item>
        <item>Thai Monastery\nWell known for its curved roof covered with exquisite tiles of gold, the Thai Monastery houses a bronze statue of Buddha and another recently erected 25m high statue in the garden.\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pondicherry">
        <item>Auroville\nAuroville is one of those towns which appear to come to life right out of fiction. In the union territory of Pondicherry, this township runs on the principles of peace, harmony, sustainable living and \'divine consciousness\' which was the philosophy of the Mother of Sri Aurobindo Society, Mirra Alfassa. This universal township was inaugurated on 28 February 1968 with the agenda that it will be a place with people willing enough to make this a hub of uninterrupted education and progress, regardless of their caste, creed, nationality or race. Called the city of dawn, this place is the epitome of tranquility and proves as the perfect escape for the ones in search of peace.\n</item>
        <item>Arikamedu\nArikamedu are the ruins which carried the remnants of the Roman trade in India. Recent excavations have brought out wine jars and ancient roman coins hinting on the Roman links in the ancient history of Pondicherry.\n</item>
        <item>Aurobindo Ashram\nThe Sri Aurobindo Ashram, a spiritual community or ashram located in Pondicherry, is the outcome of a small community of disciples who had gathered around Sri Aurobindo after he retired from politics and settled in Pondicherry in 1910. On 24 November 1926, after a major spiritual realization, Sri Aurobindo withdrew from public view in order to continue his spiritual work. At this time he handed over the full responsibility for the inner and outer lives of the spiritual aspirants and the ashram to his spiritual collaborator, the Mother earlier known as Mirra Alfassa. This date is therefore generally known as the founding-day of the ashram.\n</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>